<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TheMadBlogger.com - Internet&apos;s Premier Waste You in a Video Game Disposal Service</title>
    <description>You likely upset me!</description>
    <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.themadblogger.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 03:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 03:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roofing and Exterior Pros in Ellisville, Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;!--
[Check out the type of folks that work at Roofing and Exterior Pros](https://twitter.com/Citizens4STL/status/1716438318122967367)

&gt; Yesterday, Sunday, at ~8:30 AM at 10th &amp; Clark, we witnessed a guy beat the s&amp;@$ out of a guy in a road rage incident. The victim made the mistake of honking at him for running a red light. He then made the mistake of leaving his door unlocked.  
&gt; The assailant was in his work truck — Roofing and Exterior Pros. 314-791-1622. He dragged the victim from his car, beat him to the ground, including kicking him in his face. The victim will need stitches.  
&gt; We called 911. For some reason no police report exists at this time. But hey, crime is down.  
&gt; The assailant then followed a Range Rover that also honked at him during the incident. The assailant began to shoot a gun at the Range Rover during a car chase in Downtown. See attached photos. 


and of course from [an online review](https://www.trustindex.io/reviews/roofingandexteriorpros.com):

&gt; This morning in downtown St. Louis, I watched the driver of a Roofing &amp; Exterior Pros truck leave his vehicle to assault a driver who made the mistake of honking at him. The passenger of the Roofing &amp; Exterior Pros truck also left the vehicle apparently to provide the driver with backup. The victim suffered numerous severe injuries to his face as the Roofing &amp; Exterior Pros driver punched and kicked him repeatedly.  
&gt; I&apos;ve posted photos of the assault. The SLMPD has better video of the event, but I am not allowed to post them.  
&gt; The driver than exchanged words with a driver of another vehicle and then started to chase the vehicle through the streets of downtown. Per SLMPD, the driver of the Roofing &amp; Exterior Pros truck shot numerous times at the vehicle being chased.  
&gt; I reluctantly write this but feel it&apos;s important that the public is aware of this company&apos;s behavior.  

Really curious if one of the gentleman in the photo are the owner Jake Ehlinger the &quot;owner&quot; though his wife is on record with the state as the owner, or if they&apos;re just employees. Either way, not a good look for the company.

If you&apos;re looking for a roofing company in St. Louis County be sure to look for anyone but Roofing and Exterior Pros!

Probably won&apos;t find them online anyways, looks like their Facebook page, Google Listing and other social media profiles are all gone!



--&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/roofingandexteriorpros</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/roofingandexteriorpros</guid>
        
        
        <category>bad</category>
        
        <category>roofing</category>
        
        <category>stl</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pro-Tec Pest Management</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The drivers at Pro-Tec Pest Management drive like assholes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving to the doctor’s office this morning, TMB is cruising along, follow the speed limit, in the left lane getting ready to get into the turn lane at the stop light coming up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along the passenger side pulls a pickup truck (a baby one at that) at a stop light. We’re in a school zone, school is in session, the lights are flashing. Speed limit 30 MPH in the school zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The driver of the Pro-Tec Pest Management pickup truck takes off from the light, accelerating to at least 45-50 MPH in order to pass The Mad Blogger, in the 1/8th of a mile between lights. Photo taken after they passed  and then had to wait for another signal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good job asshole, TMB hopes your company docks your pay or fires you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for pest management in St. Louis County be sure to look for anyone but Pro-Tec Pest Management.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/pro-tec-pest-management</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/pro-tec-pest-management</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Problem with the World Today is Talking Heads</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;TMB had a revalation today. After spending far too many hours responding to right wing nut jobs about CRT and the threat of CRT to Rockwood School District (hint, there is no threat).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMB has decided, decreed as it may be, that Talking Heads are the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should read the news. From multiple sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should use the things you learned in school (or should have learned in school, which is another problem that is splitting America today), to determine what is factual, and what is simply fake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A person who is paid to have a talk show, be it radio, TV, or online, is paid to get you to listen. They are paid to get you riled up and listening more and more. The way they commonly do that is to spew bullshit out of their mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critical Race Theory is not invading the public school system. Far from it. History, truth, is invading our school system. Teaching our kids about how the world IS and how it CAME TO BE. That’s how they learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop listening to the talking heads. Seriously, sports talk, talk radio, whatever, it is all a waste of time. They are saying what they need to say to get viewers/listeners and generate advertising revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go outside. Take a hike. Ride you bike. Mow your lawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do something productive, don’t listen to the talking heads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Mad Blogger (Talking Head) signing off for the night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/talking-heads-are-the-problem</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/talking-heads-are-the-problem</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Airport Shuttles 921 and 978</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are in the Bay Area and are looking for a ride to the Airport, be sure to NOT use Pacific Airport Shuttles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning (around 7:45am pacific time) on the way to work (11/17/2011) TMB was cut off by two of Pacific Airport Shuttles vans, number 921 and 978. They were headed up 92 from Half Moon Bay, and after having been caught up in traffic where the highway merges from 2 lanes to 1, they decided to cut around cars after the “do not pass” signs and move up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very rude thing to do as drivers, and it wasn’t just one of them, but both vans did this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mad Blogger won’t be using Pacific Airport Shuttles anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/Pacific-Airport-Shuttles-921-and-978</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/Pacific-Airport-Shuttles-921-and-978</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Good Cook Classic Meat Thermometer NSF Approved SUCKS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, here is one to get TMB all worked up. The Mad Blogger should have learned his lesson a few months back when trying to cook a tri-tip on the ole BBQ out back, but he didn’t, so history repeated itself on December 25, 2011. The Good Cook Classic Meat Thermometer NSF Approved, pictured, has to be one of the worst designed products of all time. Take a look at that photo. That photo is taken at room temperature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you start cooking your bird, and you follow the directions, a 20-24 lb bird will likely take between 4.5 and 5 hours, at least according to the packaging on our turkey. At about 3.5 hours TMB decides that it is time to check the temperature on the bird, the instructions say the internal temperature of the turkey should be at least 165 degrees to ensure it is fully cooked. Grab your trusty meat thermometer, and stick is in the bird, watch the needle spin. Wait, which needle are we wathing for?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exactly. There is a red needle, and a black needle, but how are you supposed to know which needle is for the temperature, and which is for the “doneness”. There are no instructions, there is nothing written on the display to give you a hint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only way to read this is (based on my testing, against another thermometer) the BLACK needle measures the temperature, so you need to stick it in the bird you are measuring and wait for it to spin around the dial. Wherever the black needle stops is the current (or close to) temperature. The Mad Blogger googled some results, but found posts stating both the Black and the Red needle are used for the temperature, so obviously there is a ton of confusion out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “GoodCook” website doesn’t even show you a details page for this thermometer anymore, you have to go and find it in a Cached version from google, I can only imagine this is because they don’t have any faith in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This product has to have the worst User Experience and ease of use of any product I have ever purchased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DO NOT BUY&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/The-Good-Cook-Classic-Meat-Thermometer-NSF-Approved-SUCKS</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/The-Good-Cook-Classic-Meat-Thermometer-NSF-Approved-SUCKS</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Movie Theater in Wildwood, Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;update&quot;&gt;Update&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 1 month, we finally got B&amp;amp;B Theaters to process a proper refund. Unsure if we will ever go back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;original-post&quot;&gt;Original Post&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is one movie theater in Wildwood Missouri, and based on poor customer service experiences with B&amp;amp;B Theaters in Wildwood, it is not our recommendation that you patronize their theater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you purchase tickets for a movie online, you will be charged a service fee. If that movie is for some reason cancelled, they will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not inform you ahead of time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not refund you the full price you paid for the tickets and the service fee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck getting B&amp;amp;B Theaters to respond to you either. While they might actually respond to a “review” posted on Google Maps ratings, they won’t go any further than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;please-check-out-one-of-these-theaters-close-to-wildwood&quot;&gt;Please check out one of these theaters close to Wildwood:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amctheatres.com/movie-theatres/st-louis/amc-classic-chesterfield-14&quot;&gt;AMC Chesterfield 14 located in the Chesterfield Mall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marcustheatres.com/theatre-locations/marcus-chesterfield-galaxy-14-mega&quot;&gt;Marcus Theaters in Chesterfield, Missouri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever you walk into the B&amp;amp;B Theaters in Wildwood, Missouri you are just about guaranteed to walk into a smokey (burnt popcorn) room with very poor customer service being provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please avoid the B&amp;amp;B Theaters in Wildwood, they will just steal your money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;theft-from-bb-theaters-in-wildwood-missouri&quot;&gt;Theft from B&amp;amp;B Theaters in Wildwood, Missouri&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We finally got someone to respond to us on Twitter after reaching out to B&amp;amp;B Theaters, and they replied that they will not refund the transaction fees. So ultimately the theater sold tickets to provide a service, cancelled the showing of the movie, and then will not refund the full amount charged.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/wildwood-missouri-movie-theater/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/wildwood-missouri-movie-theater/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Injen Systems Customer Service Sucks</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So TMB has been trying for 4+ months now to get some customer service from Injen Systems for the Super SES Exhaust on their Nissan 350z that has a massive leak in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in August TMB received a response from Injen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote &gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi TMB,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you send me a picture of your exhaust? I guess we had a few different ones made for that same vehicle and a photo would make it much easier to figure out what part and get you the correct part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TMB responded with photos of the exhaust and what they needed. TMB has heard nothing back. They&apos;ve emailed them multiple times, even emailing their tech and info email addresses, but so far TMB has not received a single response from them since that email quoted above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMB sure wishese they could get some help, previously TMB actually liked the exhaust on my 350z, but this has to be the worst customer service ever!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Good News! Injen came through! The car is all back to normal now and the leaky pipes were replaced!  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.project350z.com/injen-super-ses-installation-on-the-350z&quot;&gt;https://www.project350z.com/injen-super-ses-installation-on-the-350z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/Injen-Systems-Customer-Service-Sucks</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/Injen-Systems-Customer-Service-Sucks</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A word of warning for the Samsung LN40C630K1F</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Mad Blogger is back! For this post TMB is a little torn. TMB isn’t actually ranting, just giving people a word of warning, and some praise at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A month ago TMB moved, and because of that decided that it was time to get a new TV for the bedroom, rather than moving the old CRT across the country. So TMB picked up a Samsung 40’ LCD TV that did 1080p and 120mhz, the model was LN40C630K1F and it was purchased from Best Buy. All seemed well at first, the TV performed great, until TMB noticed something, a blue pixel on the screen, when it shouldn’t be blue. So after about a week (of the bad pixel) the TV went back to Best Buy to get exchanged for another of the same model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I brought this new TV home and hooked it up, everything was great for a few minutes then the TV was attacked by some red vertical lines, which eventually turned to black.TMB checked connections, restarted everything, with no change. Eventually the lines went away, but they came back a few times throughout the week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today TMB took the TV back to Best Buy and picked up a 40’ Sony LCD. Thanks to Best Buy for the great customer service! They were extremely helpful throughout the whole process. TMB went ahead and purchased their 4yr protection plan for the new TV, just in case anything goes wrong with this one.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/A-word-of-warning-for-the-Samsung-LN40C630K1F</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/A-word-of-warning-for-the-Samsung-LN40C630K1F</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don&apos;t trust Glenn Hyundai in Kentucky</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&apos;re shopping for a car, TMB highly recommends you stay away from Glenn Hyundai in Lexington Kentucky. There are a few stories going around on the internet in which a sales guy at Glenn Hyundai put the car on Ebay, and now won&apos;t sell the car at the final selling price of the auction. Even threatening the buyer with a lawsuit if he doesn&apos;t stop posting on the internet. You can find more on the story from &lt;a href=&quot;http://jalopnik.com/5453145/kentucky-hyundai-dealer-wont-honor-ebay-auction-deal-calls-buyer-psycho&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jalopnik&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.autoblog.com/2010/01/20/hyundai-dealer-auctions-genesis-coupe-for-16k-doesnt-want-to/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Autoblogs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/P&gt;

&lt;P&gt;Sounds like something &lt;a href=&quot;/Dont-go-to-Glendale-Chrysler-in-St-louis-MO&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Glendale Chrysler&lt;/a&gt; would try to pull, don&apos;t shop there either! They have previously employed people who steal identities from car buyers. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/Dont-trust-Glenn-Hyundai-in-Kentucky</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/Dont-trust-Glenn-Hyundai-in-Kentucky</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bringing sexy back</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;TMB thinks it is time to bring back the site. The Mad Blogger is back baby, look out.&lt;/P&gt;

&lt;P&gt;Here are some of our previous &apos;best&apos; posts &lt;/P&gt;

&lt;P&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Dont-go-to-Glendale-Chrysler-in-St-louis-MO&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Why you shouldn&apos;t go to Glendale Chrysler&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/P&gt;

&lt;P&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Charter-Communications-Still-Sucks&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Charter Communications Still Sucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/P&gt;

&lt;P&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Why-not-to-buy-from-Southtown-Dodge-AKA-Southtown-Dodge-Sucks&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Southtown Dodge has bad sales people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/P&gt;

&lt;P&gt;Stay tuned for more rants coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.themadblogger.com/Bringing-sexy-back</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.themadblogger.com/Bringing-sexy-back</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
